<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title>Alternative Friday Factorio Fan Facts</title>
  <link href="https://alt-f4.blog" rel="self" />
  <id>https://alt-f4.blog/</id>
  <updated>2021-10-29T18:35:01+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Therenas</name>
    <uri>https://alt-f4.blog/about</uri>
    <email>AlternativeFridayFacts@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #50 -  Zajímavosti Raketovéhi Sila</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/cs/ALTF4-50/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-50</id>
    <updated>2021-10-29T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Tento týden je zlaté výročí Alt-F4, vzhledem k tomu, že je 50. edice. Žádné speciální festivity ale nejsou, děláme je až moc často. Místo toho, &lt;em&gt;garr890354839&lt;/em&gt; přispívá svým prvním článkem, v kterém mluví o některých podivnostech a trochu matiky ohledně raketových sil. Poté, &lt;em&gt;everLord&lt;/em&gt; nám řekne o nové komunitní události...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #49 - Dyworld Release Party</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/cs/ALTF4-49/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-49</id>
    <updated>2021-10-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;After an involuntary two-week break (please join our &lt;a href=&quot;https://alt-f4.blog/discord&quot;&gt;Discord&lt;/a&gt; to contribute your amazing article &lt;em&gt;hint hint nod nod&lt;/em&gt;), Alt-F4 is back with issue #49! There’s two returns in one week actually, as &lt;em&gt;Dysoch&lt;/em&gt; returns to talk about Dyworld once again, this time about the release party and all the...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #48 - Angel's Automated Unit Tests</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/cs/ALTF4-48/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-48</id>
    <updated>2021-09-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;After a long while, an ancient contributor by the name of &lt;em&gt;Lovely_Santa&lt;/em&gt; is back in his writing pen! We’ve last heard from our hero all the way back in &lt;a href=&quot;https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-2/&quot;&gt;Issue #2&lt;/a&gt; where he was experimenting with the modding abilities of the new (at the time) Spidertron. This time, he...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #47 - Optimizing the Solution</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/cs/ALTF4-47/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-47</id>
    <updated>2021-09-17T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;After a three-week hiatus, Alt-F4 is back, more motivated than ever! We start off with a bang as &lt;em&gt;ilbJanissary&lt;/em&gt; goes into depth about how the calculation engine behind &lt;a href=&quot;https://factoriolab.github.io&quot;&gt;FactorioLab&lt;/a&gt; does its magic. It might seem complicated at the surface, but the process is broken down into granular parts that...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #46 - One Year And Counting</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/cs/ALTF4-46/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-46</id>
    <updated>2021-08-20T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Oh man. It really has been a year since I started this project. Can’t quite believe it’s already been a year, while also not quite believing the project carried on for a whole year. In the beginning, it was just a silly idea that I wanted to try out and...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #45 - Satisfactorio</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/cs/ALTF4-45/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-45</id>
    <updated>2021-08-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;For issue #45, Alt-F4 has another mod spotlight to share, with the twist that the issue will be released alongisde the &lt;a href=&quot;https://mods.factorio.com/mod/Satisfactorio&quot;&gt;mod&lt;/a&gt; itself! &lt;em&gt;Niet&lt;/em&gt; has been plugging away at bringing some of Satisfactory’s mechanics to Factorio, and it’s way more involved than just bringing over the recipes and calling...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #44 - A New Perspective</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/cs/ALTF4-44/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-44</id>
    <updated>2021-07-30T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;You remember April Fool’s day this year? Was quite a while ago already, but if you visited the subreddit on that day, you probably saw &lt;em&gt;arrow in my gluteus maximus&lt;/em&gt;’s mind-bending video. If not, this week’s issue #44 of Alt-F4 will catch you up and then go over how exactly...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #43 - The DyWorld Saga</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/cs/ALTF4-43/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-43</id>
    <updated>2021-07-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;In issue #43 of Alt-F4, mod-maker extraordinaire &lt;em&gt;Dysoch&lt;/em&gt; talks about his history of modding (which started all the way back in Factorio 0.7!), giving a bit of an overview of how his mods evolved over time. Then, he goes into his latest and greatest project that’s due for release very...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #42 - The Meaning of Automation</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/cs/ALTF4-42/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-42</id>
    <updated>2021-07-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;In this week’s issue #42 of Alt-F4, after &lt;a href=&quot;https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-34/&quot;&gt;previously&lt;/a&gt; investigating the games that influenced Factorio, we’ll now be looking at how Factorio influenced the automation genre as a whole, if that’s even a thing. Maybe it isn’t. After 7.5 million years of contemplation, &lt;em&gt;Nanogamer7&lt;/em&gt; has an answer, and it...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #41 - Title loading, please stand by ...</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/cs/ALTF4-41/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-41</id>
    <updated>2021-07-09T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This week, for issue #41, &lt;em&gt;oof2win2&lt;/em&gt; returns with a somewhat more technical article about what exactly can go wrong when trying to connect to multiplayer games and how to potentially solve these issues. If you’ve ever wondered why Factorio wouldn’t let you join your friends’ multiplayer game, this article might...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
</feed>
