<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title>Alternative Friday Factorio Fan Facts</title>
  <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/atom.xml" rel="self" />
  <id>https://alt-f4.blog</id>
  <updated>2021-05-28T13:19:40+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Therenas</name>
    <uri>https://alt-f4.blog/about</uri>
    <email>AlternativeFridayFacts@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #37 - Combinator Crash Course Continuation</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-37/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-37</id>
    <updated>2021-05-28T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;On the 37th week during which an issue of Alt-F4 is being released, we present: Issue #37! What a surprise! In it, long-time contributor &lt;em&gt;pocarski&lt;/em&gt; is back with yet more very approachable explanations of how you can spice up and optimize your base with but a few combinators!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;combinators-2-augmented-logistics-pocarski&quot;&gt;Combinators...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #36 - The Nauvian Perspective: Bentham and Xisumavoid</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-36/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-36</id>
    <updated>2021-05-21T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This week brings back &lt;em&gt;The Nauvian Perspective&lt;/em&gt; for the second time, which involves talking to Factorio personalities about life, the universe, and everything. This time, &lt;em&gt;Bobby&lt;/em&gt; had a little chat with Bentham aka. MangledPorkGaming about the very early years of Factorio’s existence.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;the-nauvian-perspective-bentham-and-xisumavoid-bobby&quot;&gt;The Nauvian Perspective: Bentham and Xisumavoid &lt;author&gt;Bobby&lt;/author&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #35 - Do you even lift bro?</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-35/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-35</id>
    <updated>2021-05-14T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;In the middle of May, in a very expected fashion, issue #35 of Alt-F4 is here for you to consume through your eyeballs. On offer is a scientific exploration by &lt;em&gt;Romner&lt;/em&gt; of why exactly the Factorio engineer is much more of a chad than Minecraft Steve. To round this feast...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #34 - How Did We Get Here?</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-34/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-34</id>
    <updated>2021-05-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This week’s issue #34 has &lt;em&gt;Nanogamer7&lt;/em&gt; start on a potential new series of articles about the very origins of Factorio. This week features a dive into potential inspirations for this masterpiece of a game, with a diversion into game design here or there. Stay awhile and listen!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;the-best-of-its-genre--factorio-origins-nanogamer7&quot;&gt;The Best...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #33 - Vanilla: Shaken, not Stirred</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-33/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-33</id>
    <updated>2021-04-30T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;In this delightful issue #33 of Alt-F4, &lt;em&gt;Villfuk02&lt;/em&gt; presents their most recent mod creation: The Recipe Randomizer! A spotlight is put on all the design problems that needed to be overcome to make a recipe randomizer that is actually good. After that, &lt;em&gt;redlabel&lt;/em&gt; announces the most recent COMFY event, which...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #32 - Operation Wireshark</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-32/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-32</id>
    <updated>2021-04-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the shark-filled issue #2⁵ of Alt-F4. In these treacherous waters, &lt;em&gt;The-Kool&lt;/em&gt; guides us towards putting speakers to good use, maybe even as a shark-warning-system, in the latest episode of Complexity Corner! Then, &lt;em&gt;Hornwitser&lt;/em&gt; gets to some actual shark hunting using Wireshark, telling the story of how he tracked...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #31 - Combinator Crash Course</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-31/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-31</id>
    <updated>2021-04-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;After a quick one-week break, Alt-F4 is back with issue #31. In it, &lt;em&gt;pocarski&lt;/em&gt; returns to talk about yet more ways to build computer logic in Factorio, featuring combinators this time, which turn out to be simpler to use than you’d think! Afterwards, &lt;em&gt;Big Community Games&lt;/em&gt; announce another exciting event...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #30 - The Nauvian Perspective: Zisteau</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-30/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-30</id>
    <updated>2021-04-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Crossing into the realm of numbers that start with a three, issue #30 has stringweasel bringing a bit of a new format to Alt-F4: an interview, sort of. He talked to YouTube famous person Zisteau about his perspective on various topics relating to this game of ours.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3 id=&quot;the-nauvian-perspective-zisteau-stringweasel&quot;&gt;The Nauvian...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #29 - Beacons and Not Belts</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-29/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-29</id>
    <updated>2021-03-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This week, for issue #29, we have a rare double feature again! First up, TheKool, who can’t stop talking about modules, rounds out his &lt;em&gt;Complexity Corner&lt;/em&gt; saga by talking about beacons and what they are good for. Then, oof2win2 returns to put the spotlight on their mod &lt;em&gt;No Belts&lt;/em&gt;, which...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
</feed>