<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title>Alternative Friday Factorio Fan Facts</title>
  <link href="https://alt-f4.blog" rel="self" />
  <id>https://alt-f4.blog/</id>
  <updated>2022-05-27T13:55:12+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Therenas</name>
    <uri>https://alt-f4.blog/about</uri>
    <email>AlternativeFridayFacts@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #61 - Draftsman: A Python module for creating blueprints</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/es/ALTF4-61/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-61</id>
    <updated>2022-05-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;For this week’s issue of Alt-F4, we return to the roots of being a spiritual successor to the &lt;em&gt;FFF&lt;/em&gt; by going deep on a technical topic. To that end, &lt;em&gt;redruin1&lt;/em&gt; presents his newest invention: Factorio Draftsman. Sure, there have been other projects trying to build a library for generating blueprints...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #60 - Burning Questions</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/es/ALTF4-60/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-60</id>
    <updated>2022-05-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;On the diamond anniversary of Alt-F4, local madman &lt;em&gt;Sir Fendi&lt;/em&gt; returns once again with a deep dive into Factorio’s thermodynamics. Or, said another way, he wants to find out how &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt; can get the most out of your coal by further processing it into different fuels. Isn’t that nice of...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #59 - r/place 2022: A Pixelated Tale</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/es/ALTF4-59/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-59</id>
    <updated>2022-04-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A couple of weeks after the chaos that was r/place, resident historian &lt;em&gt;stringweasel&lt;/em&gt; took it upon himself to go through the chronology of how the Factorio community tried to leave its mark on the canvas. Battles were fought, alliances were forged, and a lot of fun was had! If the...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #58 - Mods for Your Swamp</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/es/ALTF4-58/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-58</id>
    <updated>2022-04-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;For no special reason, on this particular Friday, &lt;em&gt;Sir Fendi&lt;/em&gt; took it upon himself to highlight up a few humorous mods that might not be useful, but sure are fun. We’ll start with mods that only change visuals or audio to add some unique flavors to your engineering experiences. Afterwards,...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #57 - Nuclear Energy and You</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/es/ALTF4-57/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-57</id>
    <updated>2022-03-04T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Another week, another Alt-F4 …? I guess we’ve been away for a while. It’s totally because we didn’t want to steal the spotlight from the &lt;a href=&quot;https://factorio.com/blog/&quot;&gt;FFF&lt;/a&gt;, which returned this year! Either way, let’s stop distracting from the great piece we &lt;em&gt;do&lt;/em&gt; have this week: First-time contributor &lt;em&gt;Sir Fendi&lt;/em&gt; wrote...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #56 - Factorio's Early Days</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/es/ALTF4-56/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-56</id>
    <updated>2021-12-31T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;For the last Alt-F4 of the year, on the very last day of the year, we wanted to take a look back at &lt;em&gt;ye olden&lt;/em&gt; days of Factorio. Back when it was still a diamond in the rough, with definite potential, but concrete issues and annoyances as well. We hit...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #55 - The Dark Alleys of Modding</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/es/ALTF4-55/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-55</id>
    <updated>2021-12-17T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;For issue #55 of Alt-F4, &lt;em&gt;stringweasel&lt;/em&gt; prepared a very special treat for everyone, getting various modders to talk about the deepest, dankest hacks they’ve come up with to make their mods work. We’ve got MagmaMcFry, raiguard, Deadlock989, Anachrony, PFQNiet, and Earendel all confessing their sins!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;modding-behind-the-scenes-stringweasel&quot;&gt;Modding Behind The Scenes...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #54 - Story Missions: The Story</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/es/ALTF4-54/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-54</id>
    <updated>2021-12-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;For the first issue in the last month of the year, first-time contributor &lt;em&gt;GreenFlag&lt;/em&gt; presents their first big modding project that aims to add a proper RTS-style campaign to the game, in the spirit of the game’s tutorial levels. It’s pretty involved, and a lot of fun!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3 id=&quot;story-missions-the-story-greenflag&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://mods.factorio.com/mod/Story-Missions&quot;&gt;Story...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #53 - Laziness through Automation</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/es/ALTF4-53/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-53</id>
    <updated>2021-11-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;For the very prime real estate of issue #53 of Alt-F4, grandmaster &lt;em&gt;Therenas&lt;/em&gt; himself returns to grace us with another article. Following up his &lt;a href=&quot;https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-1/&quot;&gt;previous&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-17/&quot;&gt;masterpieces&lt;/a&gt; that mostly talk about his own mods, here’s more words about exactly those things. Those words explore the topic of automatically taking...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #52 - Fluidic Power Benchmarking</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/es/ALTF4-52/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-52</id>
    <updated>2021-11-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;For issue #52, &lt;em&gt;stringweasel&lt;/em&gt; returns with part two of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-51/&quot;&gt;Fluidic Power Experiment&lt;/a&gt; where he dives into the rather surprising performance implications of his creation. If you liked last week’s article, you’ll like the second part this week. What a surprise!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;the-fluidic-power-experiment-part-2-stringweasel&quot;&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://mods.factorio.com/mod/FluidicPower&quot;&gt;Fluidic Power&lt;/a&gt; Experiment: Part 2...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
</feed>
