<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title>Alternative Friday Factorio Fan Facts</title>
  <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/nl/atom.xml" rel="self" />
  <id>https://alt-f4.blog</id>
  <updated>2020-12-05T15:38:08+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Therenas</name>
    <uri>https://alt-f4.blog/about</uri>
    <email>AlternativeFridayFacts@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #16 - Modulating Pure Speed</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/nl/ALTF4-16/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-16</id>
    <updated>2020-12-04T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Another week, another issue of Alt-F4! The sixteenth week of this merry series of words to be precise. To celebrate, TheKool continues his Complexity Corner series by asking the &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Five_Ws&quot;&gt;five Ws&lt;/a&gt; about speed modules. Afterwards, DedlySpyder pontificates on how modding inspiration sometimes comes from unexpected places.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;complexity-corner-speed-modules-thekool&quot;&gt;Complexity Corner:...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #15 - Investigating 1.1</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/nl/ALTF4-15/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-15</id>
    <updated>2020-11-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This week, with 1.1 experimental just released, we take a look at two of the things it brings with it. First, &lt;em&gt;Conor_&lt;/em&gt; investigates what the new train stop limit allows him to do in his TSM-based factory. Then, &lt;em&gt;Therenas&lt;/em&gt; explores what the multithreading update to belts means, both in theory...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #14 - Exploring the Infinite</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/nl/ALTF4-14/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-14</id>
    <updated>2020-11-20T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This week &lt;em&gt;ironic toblerone&lt;/em&gt; takes us on a crazy adventure into space featuring the fantastic &lt;a href=&quot;https://mods.factorio.com/mod/space-exploration&quot;&gt;Space Exploration&lt;/a&gt; mod by &lt;em&gt;Earendel&lt;/em&gt;. Suit up and strap in, this is a fun one!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;mod-spotlight-space-exploration-ironic-toblerone&quot;&gt;Mod Spotlight: &lt;a href=&quot;https://mods.factorio.com/mod/space-exploration&quot;&gt;Space Exploration&lt;/a&gt; &lt;author&gt;ironic toblerone&lt;/author&gt;&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Space Exploration is an overhaul mod that takes you on an...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #13 - Megabase Archaeology</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/nl/ALTF4-13/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-13</id>
    <updated>2020-11-13T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;In this spookily coincidental issue 13 of Alt-F4 published on Friday 13th (it’s almost like we planned this), we focus on a single topic: building as many rocket defences as possible. What are rocket defences, you ask? Well, stringweasel is here to tell you, taking you back to a simpler...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #12 - Reverse Engineering the Spider</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/nl/ALTF4-12/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-12</id>
    <updated>2020-11-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;In this very easily divisible issue number 12 of Alt-F4, &lt;em&gt;xthexder&lt;/em&gt; goes into some of the technical behind-the-scenes regarding the bouncy spider at the bottom of the page. Then, &lt;em&gt;TheKool&lt;/em&gt; gives some newcomer-friendly insight into production modules and their uses. Finally, &lt;em&gt;T-A-R&lt;/em&gt; shares some info on an upcoming community event...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #11 - Scientific Curiosities</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/nl/ALTF4-11/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-11</id>
    <updated>2020-10-30T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the eleventh edition of Alt-F4, bringing you both mathematical analysis and a history lesson. So, listen up, student! Pocarski took it upon themself to see whether real-world mathematics works out on Nauvis. Spoiler alert: it doesn’t. Then, stringweasel returns once again to take a look at a bit...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #10 - Verdediging van je Rijk</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/nl/ALTF4-10/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-10</id>
    <updated>2020-10-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Welkom bij de tiende editie van Alt-F4, waar we de dubbele cijfers eindelijk ingaan! Deze week keert Recon419A terug met een goed argument, deze keer over hoe je het beste de muren van je fabriek zou kunnen opzetten. Hierna doet trupen wat onderzoek en gaat hij dieper in op de...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #9 - Translation Process</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/nl/ALTF4-9/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-9</id>
    <updated>2020-10-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;After our special &lt;a href=&quot;https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-8/&quot;&gt;love letter issue&lt;/a&gt; last week, we’re back to our regularly scheduled programming this week with issue nine! TheEnemy42 gives us some insight on how the crowdsourced process of translating Factorio into many different languages works, and stringweasel continues their &lt;a href=&quot;https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-6/#nauvis-archives-how-far-weve-come-stringweasel&quot;&gt;Nauvis Archives&lt;/a&gt; series by digging into...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #8 - A Love Letter to Factorio</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/nl/ALTF4-8/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-8</id>
    <updated>2020-10-09T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;For this issue of Alt-F4 we decided to do something special: ask the community why exactly they love this game so much. Everyone was invited to submit a short piece detailing their absolute favourite thing about Factorio, which many promptly did. Here’s to one of the greatest games of all...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #7 - Megabase Mentality</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/nl/ALTF4-7/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-7</id>
    <updated>2020-10-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;We’re back, providing you with your weekly dose of Factorio content! In today’s issue 7, ChurchOrganist brings us up to speed on what has been happening with Yuoki’s mods lately, LoneWolf gives us the rundown of why decentralised smelting is clearly the way to go, and T-A-R informs us about...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
</feed>