<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title>Alternative Friday Factorio Fan Facts</title>
  <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/pt-br/atom.xml" rel="self" />
  <id>https://alt-f4.blog</id>
  <updated>2021-07-16T12:26:02+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Therenas</name>
    <uri>https://alt-f4.blog/about</uri>
    <email>AlternativeFridayFacts@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #42 - The Meaning of Automation</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/pt-br/ALTF4-42/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-42</id>
    <updated>2021-07-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;In this week’s issue #42 of Alt-F4, after &lt;a href=&quot;https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-34/&quot;&gt;previously&lt;/a&gt; investigating the games that influenced Factorio, we’ll now be looking at how Factorio influenced the automation genre as a whole, if that’s even a thing. Maybe it isn’t. After 7.5 million years of contemplation, &lt;em&gt;Nanogamer7&lt;/em&gt; has an answer, and it...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #41 - Title loading, please stand by ...</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/pt-br/ALTF4-41/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-41</id>
    <updated>2021-07-09T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This week, for issue #41, &lt;em&gt;oof2win2&lt;/em&gt; returns with a somewhat more technical article about what exactly can go wrong when trying to connect to multiplayer games and how to potentially solve these issues. If you’ve ever wondered why Factorio wouldn’t let you join your friends’ multiplayer game, this article might...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #40 - Warp Speed for Charity</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/pt-br/ALTF4-40/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-40</id>
    <updated>2021-07-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;After a semi-intentional two-week mid-summer break, Alt-F4 makes its glorious return with issue #40. In it, fan-favorite and editor extraordinaire &lt;em&gt;stringweasel&lt;/em&gt; does another one of his interviews that gets us some perspective on a Nauvis-related topic. A Nauvian Perspective, if you will. This time, he talked to &lt;em&gt;Franqly&lt;/em&gt; who’ll be...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #39 - JOSEF</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/pt-br/ALTF4-39/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-39</id>
    <updated>2021-06-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;In this week’s issue of Alt-F4 #39, which is divisible by 13 (quick maffs), &lt;em&gt;Drogiwan Cannobi&lt;/em&gt; makes their first contribution to the project by elaborating on the background and on the inner workings of his Rube-Goldberg-esque self-expanding factory that’s lovingly titled JOSEF. It’s a really cool concept that is not...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #38 - FacSTEMrio</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/pt-br/ALTF4-38/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-38</id>
    <updated>2021-06-04T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This week, our in-house technical editor decided it was a good idea to write another article himself. We weren’t so sure about that, but nobody could stop him. So, we present: &lt;em&gt;Conor_&lt;/em&gt; writing about the relation between Factorio affinity and the STEM (Science, Technology, Engineering and Mathematics) fields of study....</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #37 - Combinator Crash Course Continuation</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/pt-br/ALTF4-37/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-37</id>
    <updated>2021-05-28T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;On the 37th week during which an issue of Alt-F4 is being released, we present: Issue #37! What a surprise! In it, long-time contributor &lt;em&gt;pocarski&lt;/em&gt; is back with yet more very approachable explanations of how you can spice up and optimize your base with but a few combinators!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;combinators-2-augmented-logistics-pocarski&quot;&gt;Combinators...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #36 - The Nauvian Perspective: Bentham and Xisumavoid</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/pt-br/ALTF4-36/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-36</id>
    <updated>2021-05-21T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This week brings back &lt;em&gt;The Nauvian Perspective&lt;/em&gt; for the second time, which involves talking to Factorio personalities about life, the universe, and everything. This time, &lt;em&gt;Bobby&lt;/em&gt; had a little chat with Bentham aka. MangledPorkGaming about the very early years of Factorio’s existence.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;the-nauvian-perspective-bentham-and-xisumavoid-bobby&quot;&gt;The Nauvian Perspective: Bentham and Xisumavoid &lt;author&gt;Bobby&lt;/author&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #35 - Do you even lift bro?</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/pt-br/ALTF4-35/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-35</id>
    <updated>2021-05-14T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;In the middle of May, in a very expected fashion, issue #35 of Alt-F4 is here for you to consume through your eyeballs. On offer is a scientific exploration by &lt;em&gt;Romner&lt;/em&gt; of why exactly the Factorio engineer is much more of a chad than Minecraft Steve. To round this feast...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #34 - How Did We Get Here?</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/pt-br/ALTF4-34/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-34</id>
    <updated>2021-05-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This week’s issue #34 has &lt;em&gt;Nanogamer7&lt;/em&gt; start on a potential new series of articles about the very origins of Factorio. This week features a dive into potential inspirations for this masterpiece of a game, with a diversion into game design here or there. Stay awhile and listen!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;the-best-of-its-genre--factorio-origins-nanogamer7&quot;&gt;The Best...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #33 - Vanilla: Shaken, not Stirred</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/pt-br/ALTF4-33/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-33</id>
    <updated>2021-04-30T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;In this delightful issue #33 of Alt-F4, &lt;em&gt;Villfuk02&lt;/em&gt; presents their most recent mod creation: The Recipe Randomizer! A spotlight is put on all the design problems that needed to be overcome to make a recipe randomizer that is actually good. After that, &lt;em&gt;redlabel&lt;/em&gt; announces the most recent COMFY event, which...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
</feed>