<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title>Alternative Friday Factorio Fan Facts</title>
  <link href="https://alt-f4.blog" rel="self" />
  <id>https://alt-f4.blog/</id>
  <updated>2023-06-30T13:27:52+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Therenas</name>
    <uri>https://alt-f4.blog/about</uri>
    <email>AlternativeFridayFacts@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #65 - Factorio in Unreal Engine 5</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/pt-br/ALTF4-65/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-65</id>
    <updated>2023-06-30T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Today we’ve got a very fun project to talk about: The FUE5 project, explained in this article by &lt;em&gt;Hurricane&lt;/em&gt;. It’s Factorio, but &lt;em&gt;3D&lt;/em&gt;! Dreams do come true sometimes. It’s not quite a game, but more of a stunning re-imagining of its visuals. There’s lots of technical details on how this...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #64 - Requesting a Train</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/pt-br/ALTF4-64/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-64</id>
    <updated>2023-03-31T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;New year, same old Alt-F4! Issue #64 is not just satisfying for lovers of the binary format, but hopefully for everyone else as well. First-time contributor &lt;em&gt;OceanPhantom&lt;/em&gt; is here to share the exciting recent developments in the space of automating the train network even further via the use of modifications,...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #63 - Dana Dev Blog: Spaghetti Recipe Graphs</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/pt-br/ALTF4-63/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-63</id>
    <updated>2022-08-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;After a somewhat lengthy pause, Alt-F4 returns with an issue reminiscent of the good ol’ FFF: A dev blog! Only here, it’s not about the game itself, but a very unique and slightly crazy mod. &lt;em&gt;Credne&lt;/em&gt; brought &lt;strong&gt;Dana&lt;/strong&gt; into this world, and it took quite a bit of doing to...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #62 - AngelBob vs. Space Exploration vs Industrial Revolution</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/pt-br/ALTF4-62/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-62</id>
    <updated>2022-06-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This week’s issue #62 is an exciting one, as first-time contributor &lt;em&gt;Laurence&lt;/em&gt; makes their debut by tackling a question that a lot of you probably asked yourselves at some point: What’s the difference between some of these big modpacks again? And why might I enjoy one over the other? &lt;em&gt;Laurence&lt;/em&gt;...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #61 - Draftsman: A Python module for creating blueprints</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/pt-br/ALTF4-61/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-61</id>
    <updated>2022-05-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;For this week’s issue of Alt-F4, we return to the roots of being a spiritual successor to the &lt;em&gt;FFF&lt;/em&gt; by going deep on a technical topic. To that end, &lt;em&gt;redruin1&lt;/em&gt; presents his newest invention: Factorio Draftsman. Sure, there have been other projects trying to build a library for generating blueprints...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #60 - Burning Questions</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/pt-br/ALTF4-60/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-60</id>
    <updated>2022-05-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;On the diamond anniversary of Alt-F4, local madman &lt;em&gt;Sir Fendi&lt;/em&gt; returns once again with a deep dive into Factorio’s thermodynamics. Or, said another way, he wants to find out how &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt; can get the most out of your coal by further processing it into different fuels. Isn’t that nice of...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #59 - r/place 2022: A Pixelated Tale</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/pt-br/ALTF4-59/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-59</id>
    <updated>2022-04-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A couple of weeks after the chaos that was r/place, resident historian &lt;em&gt;stringweasel&lt;/em&gt; took it upon himself to go through the chronology of how the Factorio community tried to leave its mark on the canvas. Battles were fought, alliances were forged, and a lot of fun was had! If the...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #58 - Mods for Your Swamp</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/pt-br/ALTF4-58/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-58</id>
    <updated>2022-04-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;For no special reason, on this particular Friday, &lt;em&gt;Sir Fendi&lt;/em&gt; took it upon himself to highlight up a few humorous mods that might not be useful, but sure are fun. We’ll start with mods that only change visuals or audio to add some unique flavors to your engineering experiences. Afterwards,...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #57 - Nuclear Energy and You</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/pt-br/ALTF4-57/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-57</id>
    <updated>2022-03-04T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Another week, another Alt-F4 …? I guess we’ve been away for a while. It’s totally because we didn’t want to steal the spotlight from the &lt;a href=&quot;https://factorio.com/blog/&quot;&gt;FFF&lt;/a&gt;, which returned this year! Either way, let’s stop distracting from the great piece we &lt;em&gt;do&lt;/em&gt; have this week: First-time contributor &lt;em&gt;Sir Fendi&lt;/em&gt; wrote...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #56 - Factorio's Early Days</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/pt-br/ALTF4-56/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-56</id>
    <updated>2021-12-31T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;For the last Alt-F4 of the year, on the very last day of the year, we wanted to take a look back at &lt;em&gt;ye olden&lt;/em&gt; days of Factorio. Back when it was still a diamond in the rough, with definite potential, but concrete issues and annoyances as well. We hit...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
</feed>
