<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title>Alternative Friday Factorio Fan Facts</title>
  <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/pt-br/atom.xml" rel="self" />
  <id>https://alt-f4.blog</id>
  <updated>2021-03-20T18:02:55+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Therenas</name>
    <uri>https://alt-f4.blog/about</uri>
    <email>AlternativeFridayFacts@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #28 - ROFL</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/pt-br/ALTF4-28/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-28</id>
    <updated>2021-03-19T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This fine week in March, first-time contributor Ph.X talks about their very compartmentalized system for laying out a base using isolated modules and connecting them through a Logistic Train Network. Taking inspiration from software development and the lessons learned there, Ph.X uses the concepts of Modular Programming to their advantage.&lt;/p&gt;...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #27 - Designing the Unnecessary</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/pt-br/ALTF4-27/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-27</id>
    <updated>2021-03-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This week, pocarski continues his descent into belt-related madness by taking a look at universal balancers. The result is as crazy as it is useless, so you know we’re in for a treat!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;universal-8-8-perfectly-balanced-as-all-things-should-be-pocarski&quot;&gt;Universal 8-8: Perfectly Balanced, as All Things Should Be &lt;author&gt;pocarski&lt;/author&gt;&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-23/#belt-only-computing-part-1-not-so-quick-maths-pocarski&quot;&gt;Recently&lt;/a&gt;, I made a bunch...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #26 - Putting the Multi in Player</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/pt-br/ALTF4-26/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-26</id>
    <updated>2021-03-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;In this week’s 26th issue of Alt-F4 (half a year of issues!), oof2win2 goes into the Factorio multiplayer and explains some of the technical machinations behind it. If you’ve ever wondered what a desync is or how the game manages to handle hundreds of players and many thousands of entities...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #25 - Efficiency, Efficiency, Efficiency!</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/pt-br/ALTF4-25/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-25</id>
    <updated>2021-02-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;In this silver birthday issue of Alt-F4, TheKool returns for this third and final instalment of his series about modules. In it, he covers efficiency modules by talking about the theory and then presenting a real(ish)-world experiment!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;complexity-corner-efficiency-modules-the-kool&quot;&gt;Complexity Corner: Efficiency Modules &lt;author&gt;The Kool&lt;/author&gt;&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;This week, we’re on to the...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #24 - Criando Memórias</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/pt-br/ALTF4-24/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-24</id>
    <updated>2021-02-19T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Esta semana, estamos dando sequência ao artigo de pocarski da semana passada que era sobre como construir um computador dentro da Factorio usando apenas esteiras. Desta vez, estamos tentando ensiná-lo a lembrar das coisas. Vamos ver no que isso da.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;computação-somente-de-esteiras-parte-2-nunca-esqueçer-pocarski&quot;&gt;Computação somente de esteiras, Parte 2: Nunca esqueçer &lt;author&gt;pocarski&lt;/author&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #23 - Esteiravanza</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/pt-br/ALTF4-23/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-23</id>
    <updated>2021-02-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Depois de um hiato de duas semanas devido a alguns lançamentos quentes da FFF, estamos de volta esta semana com dois artigos sobre esteiras. No primeiro, o Recon419A explora um conceito interessante que faz com que os esteiras entreguem itens just-in-time. Então, as coisas ficam verdadeiramente nerds quando Pocarski dá...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #22 - Reclamação sobre Diagramas</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/pt-br/ALTF4-22/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-22</id>
    <updated>2021-01-22T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Para a 22ª edição de hoje da Alt-F4, &lt;em&gt;Conor_&lt;/em&gt; queria compartilhar suas fortes opiniões sobre diagramas conosco e por que eles podem te impedir de se divertir ao máximo jogando Factorio. Temos certeza de que ele ficará feliz em ouvir sua opinião a respeito, então fique à vontade para compartilhá-la...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #21 - A mais alta honra para Mods</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/pt-br/ALTF4-21/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-21</id>
    <updated>2021-01-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Esta semana, estamos de volta à nossa programação regular com mais um episódio de nossa série favorita: The Nauvis Archives! &lt;em&gt;stringweasel&lt;/em&gt; quebra os livros de história mais uma vez para mostrar alguns mods antigos e como eles eventualmente se tornaram parte da experiência base do jogo. Ao final, temos uma...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #20 - Retrospectiva 2: Boogaloo elétrico</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/pt-br/ALTF4-20/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-20</id>
    <updated>2021-01-08T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Completando os primeiros cinco meses de publicações, o Alt-F4 #20 traz a segunda parte de nossa retrospectiva e bastidores. &lt;em&gt;nanogamer7&lt;/em&gt; mostra como o processo de tradução começou e quais são alguns dos problemas que surgiram. Mas antes disso, &lt;em&gt;Conor_&lt;/em&gt; nos apresenta uma espécie de declaração de missão, que coloca nossa...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #19 - A Retrospective</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/pt-br/ALTF4-19/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-19</id>
    <updated>2021-01-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This week, in the new year, we wanted to take a look back at the project &lt;em&gt;Therenas&lt;/em&gt; started four and a half months ago to fill the void that the absence of the FFF left in all our hearts. We asked the people involved in the process about their specialty,...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
</feed>