<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title>Alternative Friday Factorio Fan Facts</title>
  <link href="https://alt-f4.blog" rel="self" />
  <id>https://alt-f4.blog/</id>
  <updated>2023-06-30T13:27:57+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Therenas</name>
    <uri>https://alt-f4.blog/about</uri>
    <email>AlternativeFridayFacts@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #65 - Factorio in Unreal Engine 5</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/zh/ALTF4-65/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-65</id>
    <updated>2023-06-30T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Today we’ve got a very fun project to talk about: The FUE5 project, explained in this article by &lt;em&gt;Hurricane&lt;/em&gt;. It’s Factorio, but &lt;em&gt;3D&lt;/em&gt;! Dreams do come true sometimes. It’s not quite a game, but more of a stunning re-imagining of its visuals. There’s lots of technical details on how this...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #64 - Requesting a Train</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/zh/ALTF4-64/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-64</id>
    <updated>2023-03-31T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;New year, same old Alt-F4! Issue #64 is not just satisfying for lovers of the binary format, but hopefully for everyone else as well. First-time contributor &lt;em&gt;OceanPhantom&lt;/em&gt; is here to share the exciting recent developments in the space of automating the train network even further via the use of modifications,...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #63 - Dana Dev Blog: Spaghetti Recipe Graphs</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/zh/ALTF4-63/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-63</id>
    <updated>2022-08-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;After a somewhat lengthy pause, Alt-F4 returns with an issue reminiscent of the good ol’ FFF: A dev blog! Only here, it’s not about the game itself, but a very unique and slightly crazy mod. &lt;em&gt;Credne&lt;/em&gt; brought &lt;strong&gt;Dana&lt;/strong&gt; into this world, and it took quite a bit of doing to...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #62 - AngelBob vs. Space Exploration vs Industrial Revolution</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/zh/ALTF4-62/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-62</id>
    <updated>2022-06-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This week’s issue #62 is an exciting one, as first-time contributor &lt;em&gt;Laurence&lt;/em&gt; makes their debut by tackling a question that a lot of you probably asked yourselves at some point: What’s the difference between some of these big modpacks again? And why might I enjoy one over the other? &lt;em&gt;Laurence&lt;/em&gt;...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #61 - Draftsman: A Python module for creating blueprints</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/zh/ALTF4-61/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-61</id>
    <updated>2022-05-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;For this week’s issue of Alt-F4, we return to the roots of being a spiritual successor to the &lt;em&gt;FFF&lt;/em&gt; by going deep on a technical topic. To that end, &lt;em&gt;redruin1&lt;/em&gt; presents his newest invention: Factorio Draftsman. Sure, there have been other projects trying to build a library for generating blueprints...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #60 - Burning Questions</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/zh/ALTF4-60/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-60</id>
    <updated>2022-05-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;On the diamond anniversary of Alt-F4, local madman &lt;em&gt;Sir Fendi&lt;/em&gt; returns once again with a deep dive into Factorio’s thermodynamics. Or, said another way, he wants to find out how &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt; can get the most out of your coal by further processing it into different fuels. Isn’t that nice of...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #59 - r/place 2022: A Pixelated Tale</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/zh/ALTF4-59/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-59</id>
    <updated>2022-04-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A couple of weeks after the chaos that was r/place, resident historian &lt;em&gt;stringweasel&lt;/em&gt; took it upon himself to go through the chronology of how the Factorio community tried to leave its mark on the canvas. Battles were fought, alliances were forged, and a lot of fun was had! If the...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #58 - Mods for Your Swamp</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/zh/ALTF4-58/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-58</id>
    <updated>2022-04-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;For no special reason, on this particular Friday, &lt;em&gt;Sir Fendi&lt;/em&gt; took it upon himself to highlight up a few humorous mods that might not be useful, but sure are fun. We’ll start with mods that only change visuals or audio to add some unique flavors to your engineering experiences. Afterwards,...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #57 - Nuclear Energy and You</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/zh/ALTF4-57/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-57</id>
    <updated>2022-03-04T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Another week, another Alt-F4 …? I guess we’ve been away for a while. It’s totally because we didn’t want to steal the spotlight from the &lt;a href=&quot;https://factorio.com/blog/&quot;&gt;FFF&lt;/a&gt;, which returned this year! Either way, let’s stop distracting from the great piece we &lt;em&gt;do&lt;/em&gt; have this week: First-time contributor &lt;em&gt;Sir Fendi&lt;/em&gt; wrote...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #56 - 异星工厂的早期时代</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/zh/ALTF4-56/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-56</id>
    <updated>2021-12-31T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;在今年的最后一期 Alt-F4 中，我们想回顾一下异星工厂的&lt;em&gt;旧时代&lt;/em&gt;。彼时它还是一块璞玉，颇具潜力但也存在问题和烦恼。我们采访了社区中的不同人士，了解他们对早期异星工厂的看法，回忆他们进入游戏的时间，以及游戏是如何变得更好的。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;回望异星工厂的早期时代多人&quot;&gt;回望异星工厂的早期时代&lt;author&gt;多人&lt;/author&gt;&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;h3 id=&quot;旧版异星工厂-jd-plays&quot;&gt;旧版异星工厂 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/jdplays&quot;&gt;&lt;author&gt;JD-Plays&lt;/author&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;嘿，我是 JD！一名 YouTuber 和 Twitch 主播，在异星工厂中浸泡了几千个小时，现已经超过了一万小时大关，但并生来如此。我是在第 13 版左右进入异星工厂的，在试玩了早期的版本后发现这个游戏并不适合我。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;所以我们来谈谈古早的异星工厂。我认为我们可以把异星工厂的时间线分成几个时代或世代。首先是现代的异星工厂，我认定包括 0.15 及以后的版本。在这个版本中，军备、生产、效能和太空科技包首次被添加到游戏中，此时基地开始以“每分钟科学”来衡量，而不是之前的标准——每分钟火箭。0.15 版到 1.1 版并没有太多的变化。当然，配方和战斗有一些小的调整，还有一两个图形更新，但是如果你给一个在 1.1 版本之前从未见过异星工厂的人一个 0.15 版本的旧拷贝，他们的主要问题是为什么没有复制和粘贴！&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h4 id=&quot;异星工厂-012---014&quot;&gt;异星工厂 0.12 - 0.14&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;这通常被称为老旧版异星工厂。有点像异星工厂还没有完全出炉的感觉。你知道正在发生什么，它看起来也很熟悉，但有些地方不对劲。首先，吸管工具。你知道，那个 Q 按键……嗯，这还不存在！锅炉是 1x1 的大小，发电的比例是 1 个泵对应 14 个锅炉对应 20 个蒸汽机。科研以紫色科学结束，但被称为外星科学包，需要外星核心来创造，你只能通过杀死虫巢来获得这些核心！这些核心也用在 3 级模块，还有动力装甲之中。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;不要误会我的意思，它仍然感觉像异星工厂，有着强大的核心游戏机制，即使它欠缺一些打磨。一切功能都和现在一样。好吧，除了蓝图，因为你必须研究它们，然后制作它们，而且要花费一个红色电路板来清除蓝图！我有没有提到过，要想获得蓝图，就必须先研究它们。哦，我有没有说过，当时要分享蓝图，我们必须以截图的形式来分享它们？是的，那时候还没有蓝图字符串的说法。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;0.11 版本也是首次加入多人游戏的时候。这远不是一个愉快的经历，因为没有像现在这样的延迟隐藏。这大约也是玩家群扩大的时期：首先是 0.11 版本带来了多人游戏，然后在...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
</feed>
