<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title>Alternative Friday Factorio Fan Facts</title>
  <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/ru/atom.xml" rel="self" />
  <id>https://alt-f4.blog</id>
  <updated>2021-04-18T14:24:19+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Therenas</name>
    <uri>https://alt-f4.blog/about</uri>
    <email>AlternativeFridayFacts@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #31 - Combinator Crash Course</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/ru/ALTF4-31/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-31</id>
    <updated>2021-04-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;After a quick one-week break, Alt-F4 is back with issue #31. In it, &lt;em&gt;pocarski&lt;/em&gt; returns to talk about yet more ways to build computer logic in Factorio, featuring combinators this time, which turn out to be simpler to use than you’d think! Afterwards, &lt;em&gt;Big Community Games&lt;/em&gt; announce another exciting event...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #30 - The Nauvian Perspective: Zisteau</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/ru/ALTF4-30/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-30</id>
    <updated>2021-04-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Crossing into the realm of numbers that start with a three, issue #30 has stringweasel bringing a bit of a new format to Alt-F4: an interview, sort of. He talked to YouTube famous person Zisteau about his perspective on various topics relating to this game of ours.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3 id=&quot;the-nauvian-perspective-zisteau-stringweasel&quot;&gt;The Nauvian...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #29 - Beacons and Not Belts</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/ru/ALTF4-29/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-29</id>
    <updated>2021-03-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This week, for issue #29, we have a rare double feature again! First up, TheKool, who can’t stop talking about modules, rounds out his &lt;em&gt;Complexity Corner&lt;/em&gt; saga by talking about beacons and what they are good for. Then, oof2win2 returns to put the spotlight on their mod &lt;em&gt;No Belts&lt;/em&gt;, which...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #28 - ROFL</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/ru/ALTF4-28/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-28</id>
    <updated>2021-03-19T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This fine week in March, first-time contributor Ph.X talks about their very compartmentalized system for laying out a base using isolated modules and connecting them through a Logistic Train Network. Taking inspiration from software development and the lessons learned there, Ph.X uses the concepts of Modular Programming to their advantage.&lt;/p&gt;...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #27 - Designing the Unnecessary</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/ru/ALTF4-27/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-27</id>
    <updated>2021-03-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This week, pocarski continues his descent into belt-related madness by taking a look at universal balancers. The result is as crazy as it is useless, so you know we’re in for a treat!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;universal-8-8-perfectly-balanced-as-all-things-should-be-pocarski&quot;&gt;Universal 8-8: Perfectly Balanced, as All Things Should Be &lt;author&gt;pocarski&lt;/author&gt;&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-23/#belt-only-computing-part-1-not-so-quick-maths-pocarski&quot;&gt;Recently&lt;/a&gt;, I made a bunch...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #26 - Putting the Multi in Player</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/ru/ALTF4-26/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-26</id>
    <updated>2021-03-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;In this week’s 26th issue of Alt-F4 (half a year of issues!), oof2win2 goes into the Factorio multiplayer and explains some of the technical machinations behind it. If you’ve ever wondered what a desync is or how the game manages to handle hundreds of players and many thousands of entities...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #25 - Эффективность, эффективность, эффективность!</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/ru/ALTF4-25/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-25</id>
    <updated>2021-02-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;В серебряный юбилей Alt-F4, TheKool возвращается с третьей и последней главой в своей серии о модулях. В ней он обьясняет модули эффективности, говоря о теории и затем представляя настоящий эксперимент!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;уголок-усложнения-модули-эффективности-the-kool&quot;&gt;Уголок Усложнения: Модули эффективности &lt;author&gt;The Kool&lt;/author&gt;&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;На этой неделе, мы на третьей и последней части Уголка Усложнения! Если вы...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #24 - Creating Memories</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/ru/ALTF4-24/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-24</id>
    <updated>2021-02-19T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This week, we’re following up on pocarski’s piece from last week that was all about how to build a computer inside Factorio using only belts. This time, we’re trying to teach it how to remember things. Let’s see how that goes.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;belt-only-computing-part-2-never-forget-pocarski&quot;&gt;Belt-only Computing, Part 2: Never Forget &lt;author&gt;pocarski&lt;/author&gt;&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;This...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Alt-F4 #23 - Beltravaganza</title>
    <link href="https://alt-f4.blog/ru/ALTF4-23/" />
    <id>https://alt-f4.blog/ALTF4-23</id>
    <updated>2021-02-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;After a hiatus of two weeks due to a couple of FFF’s hot off the presses, we’re back this week with two articles all about belts. In the first one, Recon419A explores an interesting concept that has belts deliver items in a just-in-time fashion. Then, things get truly nerdy as...</content>
  </entry>
  
  
</feed>